EPISODE 1
The urban jungle moves at a pace so
frantic that no one has a moment to spare.
If you were to describe the mankind
that lives there in a single phrase...
Homo Laundrycus.
The laundering human.
Until the day we die,
the laundry piles up again and again.
And mankind's effort to wash away
that filthy grime? It's never stopped.
Gu Pan-su, known as the Coin King,
was arrested for manipulating
the cryptocurrency market.
On appeal, he received a fine
and a suspended sentence.
The ruling has sparked debate among
victims over restitution and compensation.
You can just toss dirty laundry
into the washing machine.
But what do you do with people
who are a lost cause?
The Sand Foundation held a community
service event at Sand Haven,
a child welfare center
in Gyeonggi Province.
To mark the center's 10th anniversary,
Chairman Jeon Tae-su and 20 employees
took part in volunteer activities
and gifted sports equipment
they purchased with the donations.
Welcome to my world.
You're covered in ashes.
No matter how hard you try
to brush it off, it can't be shaken off.
What? What do you mean...
This is uncontrollable.
Yes. Every time she takes an exam,
she starts coughing.
She once got kicked out
so she wouldn't disturb other students.
Mom. That's because of asthma...
- A ghost burned to death is on her.
- What?
It must be purged from deep within.
Does that mean we need
to perform a ritual?
Mark my words or grave misfortune
will strike in November.
We can't afford a ritual right now.
This is about saving her life,
and yet you're talking about money?
Mr. Kim.
Mr. Kim!
Yes.
Get them out of my sight now.
How dare you bring these fools
into the holy shrine?
I'm sorry.
- Ye-sol, let's go. Ma'am, come with me.
- Wait...
- I didn't mean any disrespect.
- Disrespect? Leave now.
Get out of my sight!
If the truth doesn't get through
that thick skull, maybe some salt will.
Mr. Kim, throw salt at them. Salt!
Come with me. Let's go.
Usually, she's fine like that.
Ma'am, don't worry
about what she said earlier.
Ye-sol just needs to get a few more points
to get into a med school in the city.
So I pushed you too hard, I guess.
My apologies
for making you go through that.
You don't need to apologize.
I know you're worried about my daughter.
- It's here.
- Yes.
- Ye-sol.
Ma'am, take care.
Gosh, it's so tight.
Kim Deok-pil, nice.
That should be enough
to reel her in, right?
Hop in.
She'll send the money
by the end of the day.
That's the thing about the poor.
Their money is as light as a feather.
Even the neighborhood
they live in is a total dump.
Are you sure this is worth it?
You have a long way to go, Mr. Kim.
It's easier to manipulate the poor.
They barely make a living,
yet they're so greedy.
So they go all in on their kids.
I bet that woman will even sell
her store to send me the money.
You think so?
If that doesn't work out,
I bet she'd leave her kid
with her own life insurance payout.
Gosh, you make brutal jokes.
IM MI-SEON
DEPOSIT: 20,000,000
See that?
That woman is shameless.
There's only one way to win this game.
Don't be fooled by what you see.
What you see right now may be real...
But it can also be fake.
Oh, my.
Ma'am. I'm honored to meet you again.
I appreciate the warm welcome.
You look even more elegant
and beautiful today.
People would laugh if they heard that.
I mean, why else would a young boyfriend
like him be chasing after you?
She's laying it on thick.
Red!
This is our signature game,
a modern take on juryeonggu
that our ancestors used to play
while drinking.
The chance is 50-50.
The simpler the game is,
the more your blood boils.
That's what I like.
White or red.
Do you want to go
with the moon or the sun?
White.
Go with white for now.
- Let's go.
- No.
- Hey.
- Anyone else who wants to bet?
Then we'll check.
White!
White or red.
What's your choice?
- Yes!
- All right. Let's do this.
Red.
Red!
- Red!
- White!
White!
Red!
We're rich now!
2 WEEKS AGO
So this is how someone of your stature
enjoys their leisure.
We got you something we knew you'd like.
- Call it a gesture of goodwill.
- You shouldn't have.
- Oh, this is so precious.
- That was just a bonus.
This is the highlight.
What is this?
It's a waste of talent for
the great Gwiyisu of Paldalsan Mountain,
who once ruled the scene,
to put up with a young wench.
Why don't we strip your boss clean
and set up our own joint?
White and red sound different.
Red.
Red!
You should stop here for today.
Don't be like this.
Let me play a little more.
Gambling is meant to stop
when you win money.
Why do you keep telling us to leave?
You ran out of cash.
Is that it?
There's no cash?
What's going on?
If you have eyes, take a good look.
Here, we always have at least
three billion won in cash ready.
Why did you have to say that?
I'm really sorry about that.
Okay. I'll play one last round.
All in.
Ma'am, if you raise the bet--
Is it time for the young and rich boss
to step forward?
It's the last round.
You all right with that?
In that case,
we'll be switching the dealer.
Shoot.
Now, let me roll the juryeonggu.
White or red.
Between the moon and the sun,
what would you choose?
- Red?
- Red? No.
Red... Red.
Red.
- Red it is.
- Red.
Red.
Then I'll go with white.
Shall we check now?
Let's see who the goddess
of victory smiles upon.
Red.
It's red.
No way.
It's two billion.
This doesn't count.
This doesn't count! It's my money.
Let this go.
There's no way I'd make a mistake.
This doesn't count.
You're a scammer.
You said it was a 50-50 chance.
Let go!
Let this go, you prick!
You let go!
Two billion...
Leave the money behind.
Then I won't kill you.
You think it's that easy to kill someone?
What?
You think I can't?
All right.
Kill me if you can.
I dare you.
The cops are here!
It's the police! Run!
The police are here! Run!
Freeze!
Oh, long time no see, Kim Mi-yeong.
Why are you holding a sword?
That's dangerous.
Are you performing shows
at the casino now?
You must be so busy.
Oh, is this about that bag?
Bring it here.
What? Oh, the bag.
Hurry. Give it to him.
That's mine. Don't touch it.
Kim Mi-yeong.
You're under arrest for operating
an illegal gambling den
and the attempted murder of Park Tae-chun.
Put the sword down.
I'm spending my money in my establishment.
How's that illegal or attempted murder?
Are you crazy?
And the rest of you.
None of you can get out of here.
You all came here to gamble,
so don't act like you're innocent.
No one's getting out of here. No one!
She's lost it.
Take her!
No.
- Drop the sword.
- No one's leaving.
Where do you think you're going?
Deok-pil.
Baek-hwa, run.
- Deok-pil, are you okay?
- Run for your life.
Come with me.
Don't worry about me. Be happy.
Run! I said go!
Now!
Goodbye, my love!
Seriously. I thought I was going to die.
That dreadful wench.
Goodbye, my love!
That shameless kid basically
threw himself at me.
Well, I guess it's my fault.
If it's a crime to be this attractive,
then I guess I'm guilty.
Cut.
Are you going to lie there all day?
Dang, this disguise is just overkill.
Ouch. I'm too busy for this.
It stings.
This one was so much fun.
Stop laughing.
Hey, "my love"? Seriously?
Goodbye, my love!
Hey, that was in the script.
I almost got up because of you.
I only sticked to the script.
- Seriously.
- It was hilarious.
Be quiet.
Everyone, good work.
Good work.
Well done.
My money.
Two billion won...
What is all this?
What is this...
My two billion.
Kim Deok-pil, you son of a bitch!
My two billion!
CASINO OWNER HWA-RAN
STARRING YUN YI-RANG
DETECTIVE CHOI, DEALER GWIYISU
STARRING JAMES
KIM DEOK-PIL, AKA MR. KIM
STARRING MYUNG GU-HO
I can't believe you did that.
Change the dealer?
James, does that make sense to you?
What's the fun if we only stick
to the script?
The best part of a scam is the improv.
I'm all for improv,
but you need to dial it back.
You coming in like that
totally threw me off.
That's what I mean.
Still, that look on your face
wasn't so bad.
What happened there?
Did you really fall for me?
I didn't fall for you. No.
- No...
- Never mind then.
I'm hungry. How about some lobster?
Sounds good to me.
It's full-bodied,
has a delicate nose,
and there's even a subtle wisp of smoke.
Montrachet is the best white wine.
Montrachet goes down smoothly.
So? Is it France this time?
I went shopping in Paris last week,
and I bought a winery there.
Of course you'd go global
with your investments.
So how's the laundering cost this time?
Not bad.
We saved the production cost
thanks to Mr. Mustache's connection,
because he used to be on a film crew.
I love it. Amazing.
Why don't we take a trip to celebrate?
Sounds good to me. Just the three of us.
How about sky diving in Waikiki?
How'd you know? That's on my bucket list.
That was on your bucket list?
It's surfing in Waikiki,
but if I can skydive,
that's one shot two kills.
I love it.
Gu-ho, you're coming, right?
I'll sit that one out.
- What's the fun without you?
- Why?
I just don't think this line of work
really suits me.
I'm out.
My goodness.
What are you talking about?
I can't do it anymore.
Gu-ho, have you forgotten
about our promise?
Oh, the ten billion?
We cleaned that out two jobs ago.
- Did we?
- Yes.
What about you do this next job
out of loyalty?
I've got some really dirty laundry
to deal with.
So I need you.
Please? What do you say?
Please, will you?
- Please?
- I'm off. Bye for real.
Don't try to reach me. Goodbye.
Are you leaving?
Are you leaving? What about your share?
Donate the rest.
Really? Jackpot.
- Split it?
"Split it"?
Can't you say goodbye
or take care like normal people?
- Goodbye.
- Take care.
Forget it.
I'll bet my arm that he'll come back.
- I'll bet my foot on it.
- Oh, yes.
1 MONTH LATER
Hey. That hurts.
CHEONMYEONG SHOP
- What's taking you so long?
- You came just in time.
- Ma'am.
- I packed you side dishes.
I feel bad every time.
I packed it while I packed some for Bo-ra.
Don't feel bad.
- Thank you so much.
- One cone, three popsicles.
You little brats.
Do you think he's your wallet?
- Let's go.
Still, they try to be thoughtful
and avoid picking anything expensive.
Hurry up. Let's play soccer.
- I'll be right back.
- Okay.
Wait for me!
Hey. Pass.
Wait.
You need to pass better.
Go grab it.
Can you throw the ball?
Gosh.
- The ice cream...
- Look.
- What?
- What is it?
Over there.
What is it?
Cool.
What?
- What…
- What's that?
- This is weird.
- Guys, stay here.
- Okay.
It's stuffy in here.
Are you okay?
- What's happening?
- Excuse me?
Hey!
I missed you.
- Gosh. Yi-rang.
- I missed you.
What are you doing here?
Seriously!
Yi-rang, what are you doing here?
Gosh, seriously!
Yi-rang, the moment you enter my life,
you ruin the peace.
- Just like today.
- How about this interpretation?
A very quiet independent movie met me
and becomes
a wild, spectacular mega hit movie.
You know, just like the day we first met.
Look. A shooting star.
Hey, how many shooting stars
do you see a day?
If the weather is nice,
you can see 12 easily.
- Twelve?
- Yes.
That means 12 of my wishes
will come true in a day.
I like it here.
Here.
Bon appétit!
I caught them today.
They're fresh wild abalones.
So it should be fancy enough
even for your refined palate.
It's not just fancy. This is magnificent.
The texture... So yummy.
It's annoying.
Why? What is?
I mean, I expected you
to be miserable and struggling.
But with fresh food and fresh air,
you were doing better without me.
Was it fun?
You were worried about me.
You know I never worry about anything.
I guess those emotions are too much to ask
from someone who was born a sociopath.
Gu-ho.
I'm not a sociopath.
I'm sorry. I was joking.
Don't be so serious.
I'm a genius sociopath.
So call me a geniopath. I'm a geniopath.
Right. I almost forgot I never stood
a chance against a geniopath.
Just eat this.
- Gosh.
- Good.
This one's perfectly cooked.
JAMES
Why is he calling me at this hour?
Hello?
What?
What is it? What's he saying?
It's all your fault.
What?
What happened, Yi-rang?
Our plan was perfect.
What plan?
How did this happen to James?
Tell me.
Say something, Yi-rang.
Jeon Tae-su.
Jeon Tae-su?
The chairman of the Sand Foundation,
a public trust.
Ready, set, go.
SAND HAVEN SPORTS DAY
Be careful not to run into each other.
One, two, one, two.
On the outside,
he looks like an honest business man
who donates and runs an orphanage
with the money he made.
Bye, kids. See you!
- No!
- Don't go!
- I'll see you again.
- Bye.
But that's completely fabricated.
Well done, sir.
- Tell them to bathe the kids.
- Yes, sir.
Gosh.
Do you know what the most important thing
is in a relationship?
Trust, obviously. It'd be trust, sir. Yes.
You say that,
yet you miss the interest due date?
That's not it.
There's someone who refuses to vacate.
So we ran into a snag
with the land acquisition.
And because of that,
the construction got delayed.
And I couldn't retrieve the money.
Please help me, sir.
This is too much for me to handle.
How long has it been
since we've known each other?
It's been 20 years this year.
Sir.
Please.
We've spent enough time
for mountains and rivers to change twice.
You and I are basically family.
Yes, sir.
For sure, sir.
We should help each other
when things get tough.
We're family.
Right, family.
Let me settle it smoothly.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
RESTRICTED AREA
EXPECTED TO BE DEMOLISHED
NAZARETH CATHOLIC CHURCH
Hey. We're going in.
We're having seaweed soup today.
I just need to bring meat and rice.
Min-su, you're late.
Who are you?
Where do you want me to sit, Sister?
Gosh.
How can you be eating right now?
When someone's about to be buried in debt?
I'm not saying I won't leave.
I told you I need to find a place first--
Exactly.
Because of you,
we're about to end up on the street!
What are you doing?
Tear it apart.
- Yes, sir.
What are you doing?
Please stop.
Please!
Stop it.
Seriously.
Sister!
Min-su!
- Min-su.
- Get out of my way!
No.
INDEPENDENT LIVING CENTER YOUTH
ASSAULTING CONSTRUCTION EMPLOYEE
VICTIM HOSPITALIZED FOR 4 WEEKS
RELIGIOUS GROUP REMAINS SILENT
A NEW NAIL HOUSE EXPLOITING YOUTH?
Thanks to you, I was able to start
the construction on time.
It's all thanks to you.
I will serve you with all my heart.
But in reality,
he's a living legend among loan sharks.
A mere loan shark who used to lend money
to merchants and pick on gambling houses
became the biggest gang in Gangnam.
Let's start with Gwangju today.
He's called the dark godfather.
It's not enough.
He's the godfather
of the underground economy.
His so-called family is built on trust,
with him at the very top.
It's almost like a cult.
They also have strong solidarity.
One moment, they'd share
like real blood brothers, but then…
Sir.
Once one betrays, it's over.
Your life's done for.
SAND FOUNDATION
SINCE 1998
He got the tip-off that Sand Foundation's
tax evasion is being investigated.
The National Tax Service is conducting
a special investigation,
and no one knows when they will strike.
But I'm pretty sure it's tormenting him.
The public trust is only a shield
to hide his slush fund.
Rumor has it that he hid tens of billions
from the National Tax Service.
He hid it so well
that no one knows where that money is.
Anyway, now that
the investigators are closing in,
what Jeon Tae-su needs is
to take off to another country
with as much cash as he can.
KIM HAN-SU
And James approached him
at the perfect time.
I'm not worried about the cash,
but without my ID and license,
I won't be able to set sail.
I'll look into it right away.
Thank you.
Is this yours?
Yes. Thank you.
I don't know how to repay you.
No, it's okay.
- Bye now.
- One second.
I'll contact you
as soon as I return from Singapore.
CAPTAIN KIM HAN-SU
How was your trip to Singapore?
Thanks to you, I had a good trip.
Cheers.
What do you think?
It's huge.
Thank you.
I think I was lucky to meet you.
We were waiting for him to bite the bait.
Then Jeon Tae-su suddenly
reached out to us.
Captain, may I ask you for a big favor?
What's there to hesitate between us?
What can be so big?
Tell me anything.
Excuse me.
Actually there's something
I want to send abroad from Seoul.
When James couldn't reach me,
he proceeded alone.
- We're from the Customs Office!
- Who are you?
Get out of the way. We're on duty.
Make way.
- Get out.
- Get out of the way.
Open it.
- What the?
- There's nothing.
Are you saying Jeon Tae-su caught on?
Yes.
Jeon Tae-su did this to James.
PATIENT: JAMES
DIAGNOSIS: MULTIPLE FRACTURES
I should've been there.
What should I do if James doesn't wake up?
I'll do it.
Do what?
I'll take revenge for James.
No. That's too dangerous.
Then are you going to let him
get away with this?
Jeon Tae-su.
I'm going to take every penny he's got.
If that's his hell, I'll give him hell.
I'm just as angry as you are,
but this is too dangerous.
James is my family.
Isn't he yours?
- James, I suddenly got a question.
- Yes?
Who's saved as number one in your phone?
- All of a sudden?
- I'm suddenly curious.
Of course, it's you.
What are you talking about?
GU-HO
You're always my number one.
What?
Anyway, why is Yi-rang taking so long?
YI-RANG
I was always his number one.
What? You were his number one?
You're right. You got the call earlier
letting us know about his state.
What?
Then what's my number?
James.
- What's my number?
- That's not the point.
Stop it.
- Yi-rang.
- Where's his phone?
Gu-ho. Look.
- What?
- What do you think?
Like Meonggae that died
holding the enemy's general.
I'll sacrifice myself to take his revenge.
- Hey.
- How do I look?
- No. Wait right there.
- What?
- Wait right there.
- Why?
- What?
- Put that away.
Besides, it's Nongae, not Meonggae.
Never. Please don't do that.
Why not? Oh, is it too sexy?
I knew
you were the only one who cares about me.
Me?
Yes.
- No?
- No.
- I said you shouldn't because you can't.
- I can't?
Yi-rang, to be honest,
you don't have what it takes to do that.
What are you talking about?
When I have my fortune read,
they say I'm all about
being artistic and attractive.
My beauty is my biggest weapon.
Let's be honest.
Have you ever succeeded before?
What should I say about your badger game?
You're way too enthusiastic. It's scary.
You make a man's desire for romance
shrivel up and disappear.
Do you remember the laundry guy before?
He turned himself in
just to get away from you.
So we didn't get any money
and ended up spending
so much for the cost.
- And--
- Enough. Stop it.
I'll find another way.
How could you say something so mean?
You can do it.
- Get lost.
Jerk.
Have you given up on the plan?
I already have it ready.
But you were slacking off.
You get creative ideas when you slack off.
So what's your plan?
The place no one can get out,
even the president.
We already failed with the ship.
So now,
over there.
The sky.
Yes!
Ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you for flying...
Here's some fruit.
Do you need anything else?
How about some wine?
- I'm good.
- Okay.
SAND FOUNDATION HOLDS EVENT
AT THE CHILD WELFARE FACILITY
- Here.
- Do you need anything?
If you had used that brain better,
you'd be successful now.
That'd be a waste of talent.
- Oh, it's cold!
- What the? Are you kidding me?
It's so cold.
Don't you know
that I only drink Canadian water
from the North Atlantic glacier?
- Sorry. The flight schedule was mixed up.
- The flight schedule?
What's more important between your crappy
flight schedule or my high-end taste?
Did Director Choi hire you? I can tell.
Do you want me to fire you both?
Why involve him when it's my fault?
How dare you talk back to me?
I could just...
Keep it down. It's not like
you rented this plane.
Rent?
Only poor people would rent planes.
This whole plane is mine.
- Do you want to get out?
- This will only cause trouble.
- If you could please calm down...
- Don't touch me.
These pathetic losers.
Now go get me the water already!
Made from Canadian glacier ice.
I'm sorry.
- My apologies.
- It has to be from Canada.
- Watch out, man.
- You little...
My apologies.
Gosh. You can't even carry the bag?
Seriously? This is so ridiculous.
You're driving me crazy.
What are you doing?
This isn't my bag!
Seriously. This is ridiculous.
Why do you always have to drive me crazy?
Where's the car?
- I swear I didn't even touch it.
- What?
I didn't know it was your money... Sir.
Please I'm begging you.
I'll work like a dog from now on. Sir.
You still don't know your place.
You've always been a dog.
You were never anything more than that.
You'll still have to pay for the interest
before you die.
Open him up to see what we can sell
and dump his body in the ocean.
- Yes, sir.
Sir. Please give me one more chance.
That son of a bitch.
What's this?
Seriously, you're unbelievable.
This isn't my bag!
What are you going to do about my money?
What a coincidence.
Should you really be this relaxed,
Ms. Flight Attendant?
Oh, my. What brings you here?
You're more relaxed than expected.
I asked around to find you
because I was worried.
Oh, that man?
He's probably drunk by now.
Oh, my. Thank you so much.
I didn't know what to do
because I didn't even have your number.
Consider yourself lucky.
Oh, yes.
You know how to drink.
Why is life so tough?
You saw how that prick treated me, right?
He shouldn't do that
to someone's precious daughter.
Right? That's what I mean.
He's not the owner. It's his dad.
Only poor people would rent planes.
This whole plane is mine.
He's nothing more than a love child.
Oh, my goodness. What am I saying?
I'm sorry.
- I forgot what I just said.
- What?
I don't remember either.
Oh, my gosh. You're so witty.
- That cute young master--
- No, he's a horrible son of a bitch.
Do you want to go somewhere else?
- Round two?
- Round two.
Sounds good to me.
For round two.
Hi. My young master bastard.
Hey, film this.
Our young master.
Are you happy?
One's high, and the other's drunk.
What a fantastic couple.
- You are stupid.
- Yeah?
- You want to die?
- Die?
Wake up, young master.
- Hey.
- Hey. Let go.
Who the hell are you? Huh?
Hey. Put the bottle down
and fight like a man. You cheap jerk.
Fine.
Hey. I was a boxer. Bring it on.
Bring it on.
Happy?
I don't care whether you spend this money
on gambling or on drugs.
What I care about is
how you brought this money
into this country without any trouble.
This is my first time.
You have to trust me.
Are you trying
to slip out of this by yourself?
I'm doing this because I'm a newbie.
- I never--
- Sir.
I need you to take a look at this.
Here's the video
of Rising Airlines' love child.
Me? What about me? What?
RISING AIRLINES' LOVE CHILD
Check his left shoulder.
A gun?
Who are you?
YE-SOL'S
SAKWANG REAL ESTATE
Hello.
I put the restaurant on the market.
Jeong Ye-sol.
How do you know my name?
Who doesn't know about you
in this neighborhood?
Here. This is for your mom.
And if you keep faking your cough,
you'll get sick for real.
You've done well in the past,
and you continue to do quite well.
So trust yourself.
Don't let your mom visit fortune tellers.
I'm sorry.
No need to apologize to me. Bye.
What is all this?
Let's just...
call it the laundry bill.
This much evidence could lead
to a search warrant within a month.
I need to push the timeline forward.
What do you want me to do about the two?
Should I keep digging?
No one outside of these four walls
must know about our meeting.
That's how people are.
They only believe
what they can see with their own eyes.
Stop spinning that worthless brain
of yours and find a way.
That's why I kept you alive.
We can fool the X-ray by placing
a shielding device in our luggage.
It's all a set-up.
You were born to do this.
It'd be a shame
to let this talent go to waste.
What a shame.
- What?
- It was almost perfect.
You know what happens
when you fail to carry out his order?
I beg you.
We should enjoy the ending
of our project together.